[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "How has he managed to avoid public retribution for not fixing the economy better than he has done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Because this is not a normal time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What is the smart thing for America to do right now, given the ratcheting up of all the rhetoric on both sides?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I think the smart thing for us to do is to maintain constant conflict with the Israeli intelligence services and the Arab intelligence services who also don't want Iran to have a nuclear weapon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Do you trust him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "-- is they don't have a tenable position.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Do you trust Ahmadinejad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Not on this, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "If Israel was to launch an airstrike against Iran, a preemptive strike, because they believe, as appears to be the case with many of their top leadership, that Iran is right on the cusp now of developing a nuclear weapon -- if they do that, what should America's response be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I shouldn't answer that question because of my wife's position and that's the president and the security team's desire to -- a decision to make.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Iran", "Iran", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Can America -- can the world risk another flawed military action, if it turns out that Ahmadinejad is actually telling the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "First of all, it's very different from Iraq.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ahmadinejad"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "What words would you have for Mitt Romney, given the state of the election campaign right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Well, I think you know the debates are very important for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Crucial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Is he -- is he principled, do you think, Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "That's not the issue to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "How has he managed to avoid public retribution for not fixing the economy better than he has done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Because this is not a normal time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gingrich"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", ":", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "And what advice to give to Barack Obama to try and get into that kind of mindset with the Republicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well, that's the -- what Speaker Gingrich said is true, but it's not the whole truth, that is we had one year when virtually nothing got done.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 10 years"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "What is the big achievement?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "What I tried to do, when I started -- I said I'm going to give it 10 years and see where we are, if we can last 10 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Why couldn't Bill Clinton just run again and be president for the next 30 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Well, we had it for a good reason.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ireland", "Ireland"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", ":", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Are you available if it comes to -- I get this through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "LINTON: They -- there are only two countries I'm eligible to run for the leadership position is if I move to Ireland and buy a house, I can -- I can run for president of Ireland, because of my Irish heritage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What do we do about Iran and President Ahmadinejad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, this clearly will be one of the most compelling issues that the next president faces, either Obama in a second term or Romney in a first term.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ahmadinejad"], "LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["International Atomic Energy Agency"], "LOCATION": ["Tehran"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "EX", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Can the west afford to go into any kind of military conflict with Iran, with Ahmadinejad, and then discover actually all he was saying turned out to be true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, first of all, Piers, the evidence is not just intelligence services, but also the International Atomic Energy Agency that's had inspectors in there, though Tehran has interrupted and obstructed their inspections from time to time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ahmadinejad"], "LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What do you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Well, I mean, that's the dilemma in terms of turning to military action that may well be necessary at some point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What would a Romney administration do if Israel decides to go it alone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Well, I would like to make a couple points, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "I say it again, P.J. Crowley, with the benefit of hindsight and the way this has all played out, wouldn't it have been more prudent for the president to have found time in his busy television schedule to do some meetings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, he talked to Prime Minister Netanyahu the other day.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["P.J. Crowley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Williamson"]}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Is that for me, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Yes, for you, Richard Williamson.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "What is your view of the touchdown, or the Fail Mary pass, as it's now being known?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "First, I played college football.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fail Mary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "And as a European, do you fancy a bet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "LINTON: Well, on the football game, no, I did not think it was a touchdown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Hundred dollars to a charity of our choice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "You got a deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]